Really the more.  To put it bluntly, I probably haven't gone online yet, so
I opened my phone and was depressed. These things are entertaining or not.
Many people read the news as if they are supporting the team.  Slightly
for standing a little crooked, soon you will be sent a bunch of signs and
questions, many people's emotions are also unprecedentedly
fragile, when they hear the voice outside their world view, their
first reaction is not, hey, it turns out that you can think like that,
but that their identity is being attacked
, I don't know why there are some things that we can't see the
whole thing, but it's still so sure
, Truth is really the more famous, count I say the truth is more vague,
until I read Nis this book I realized, it turns out that our current
state this and humans in the past thousands of years is actually much the
same, our group has been wanting to
pursue the truth, the result is a lot of gods
щи, for feelgood, this, a bunch of former people are
a bunch of people
rules, and even came up with a vast system out specifically
to show those balls real people.
Normally everyone, I'm Ming, if the subject of the topic remember to leave a
message to tell, you might as well leave a comment and add a like
because it will be smooth, I guess this will make some people uncomfortable
.  So before we start this I prep how you treat the
content of this episode first, first, the whole video we will use an
anthropological perspective cut, not from a religious perspective, we are not
exploring the truth of God, we are exploring the history of human beings
using God to control the truth?  Second, for the sake of
explanation, I use a
chart to represent the concept in the book. Please note that the picture is not from the
book, it only reflects my personal understanding. If there are any mistakes, please
count them. I'm OK.  Third, there is the limitation of the picture
, I mixed different eras, different systems,
and religions together, it is purely a side effect of the
visual tools we understand, and not to express the
relationship between these religions scare, the last picture this looks street-
level to yeah, but actually expressing the transformation process of human beings processing
information and pursuing truth for thousands of years OKbro
now you will officially know
, how have humans pursued you since their own time?  Why is it that
our pursuit of absolute truth is getting further and further away from you?  And the most
important question, are we looking back from wine today
?   In
ancient times, if you want to manage a village of more than 1,000 people, you must have a property
, finances, fights, how to punish, marriages
, all must have laws, but if you suddenly
custom rules on the stone to follow the neighbors will stare at you and say
what to hear you know, you took the wrong drug last week in the river
colorful, you are not perfect.  People always make mistakes,
so the rules set by people will naturally be wrong. No one said that when the time comes,
we will fight.  So throughout history, it has been
discovered around the world that humans need the right to be one I am forever,
which is God.
Maybe it's on slave,
Ah Wah or fighting because you believe in a brand's belief they
generally have a part in creating the world, we let's call these
people truthfounder
CEO
Well, although it is kept
stylish, there is a death pleasure in operation.  Because this one
CEO this is long-term remote work.   The
big boss is every time personally distribute o ah and distribute KPI
to beautiful, but to go through middle
management confusion, many religions will call this
group of people called first yeah,
sacrifice yeah, and teach the representative of the west.  Islam
has Merde,
those people, that depends on what your religion?  They basically this
is God's PR, God aspect comes down yeah go to the Rain God conversation and
then back to you.  Here, this
drum Greece is one of the most famous examples, the
girl master Pithi who was able to get very seconds.  Pith is the
most senior girl teacher in Greece, you can take it for granted, she has the
temple of Apine.  And the job is to sit on a hole in the ground and suck some
unknown gas. Then, it will start to talk about some undefeated honors
.  The passage will only be open up to nine times throughout the year for you to
ask, every time this is beaten into a cake,
around 5010 BC, Athens was an exiled
Acons family, wanted to see this one girl.  why?  Because
this family wanted to push back the tyrants of Athens,
Riyass robbed the city back.   The
Maiga didn’t have an army, but luckily he had money, so he
decided to drink and go behind the scenes.  They a large northern gold, wrapped up the entire
Pineapple Temple of reconstructed marble to replace the original limestone, making the
gold forced the great super contract.  Here the girl received money, naturally
know all of every time the Badar that is the war wolf, God second request when
this, my daughter will say to him, Liberation
Panming is asking something not to pull things to feed, crops when harvesting it
.  There are people in the village stealing chickens, how to pretend, Apitia this
is loop back the same words liberated
people is no motive to stir up the relationship with Ya is not bad, but the
result of the god An ர்கள் love to fight bigger than the sky boss,
finally sent troops Ya overthrew the tyrant, the family
finally succeeded in taking over the name of democracy
.  On that day, anthropology is very important, it turns out that
heaven can be bought, sacrifices are people, there are politics,
there are bankaccounts have conflicts of interest, he
can change his own boss to take advantage, maybe even
no branch, just a moment not to save sleep, stuffy things are not determined, naturally
corrupt humans are always unbelievable, we found that a
truth can not be solved
The method is very straightforward, divide the person's involv
, fired the class.
After firing the group, humanity's new this is to me unless the
CEO white and black paper it, the truth as down stone shedding skin quilt
, humans can not change, dare to serve it.  That's how the classics are taught
Always Correct Can and Shakeable Perfection, Victory is the
most bent information technology in human history.  The CEO's switched from voice
, and can copy and paste a message.  Here,
this oil teaching is the most original beauty of ordering rice sleep Berne
sexual scripture this is not erased, copyists copy flow the punctuation good
, are afraid to offend the sky, perfectly opened the human stain.  But
is that really true?
If the perspective of ancient studies, the system fortune already has.
In the 20th century, some scholars led a group in the Dead Sea of ​​Consciousness to dig up
to the most guessed
scripture Dead Sea
ūs this has the Bible in which we are familiar with the founding of but at the same time have
found more than 20 other external books,
is you today open the mainstream Bible can not find.  The book
is full of detailed language about the devil ah and the human race has
new characters.  Seven years ago I went on a consciousness trip, came here
, so ah tour guide said a shepherd boy, because he wanted to find the
sheep of the walking room group, the old stone into the movement, but
broke the crown, first outside for out of this batch of finished before the third
century stock roll problems come to live this hole near the people obviously
believe that this version is positive.  So why has it
fallen into history today?  Who decided to leave his?
Depending on who you ask, if you ask the theologian's, he
will probably believe this one of the employee manuals, it's falling from the sky,
early nailed with all the catalog, inside no, so no.  But
if you ask a scholar, he will tell you that He was
debated by contemporary Labi sitting together at different historical periods
, Labi is taught by the miracle personnel that is, scholars, if there are
first called brother, some high-level officials are not too crying, want to
bite him away,
Which chapter passes Shen.
Which chapter will be like down so dinged
by the shot version, but by the board composed of the board of directors table power, we
can not remember, we were initially trying to find ways to avoid as a
mistake right, but the responsible group are all opinionated
people, scholar Harrari called this kind of
absolutely correct fantasy.  Hundreds of years have passed?  We simply
forget what all those people looked like?  It's fed, dead without proof right
, later generations as right this book is 100% God
restoration, the word is sacred not
this employee manual actually has a fatal, it is
readonly.  For example, there are rules that
say inaccurate numbers are too taught.  In ancient times, this rule was actually very reasonable
, because the teachers in the next village would be too stupid, and
others stayed just to admit that they had it, not some cosmic
divine law.  But thousands of years later, some people look at the electrical port
and hate it, the morning show, it turned into
a god debate, and raised it, and taught and explained
, the rest is not allowed to work, the original intention is good, to
ensure workers have a head ah, but the book does not say
technically, what is called dead work,
so bad feeding is not considered to do bad things?  We know
, in ancient times D written for the shepherd human body, how he guessed
what the world would become in the future, the result is not a joke or scare, the
Jews of modern politics, is before the beginning of the Sabbath, a
step of tissue spare.  Later there is also the battery so ah La this to say so the
button this is equivalent to ignition loss.  So just in case, what if you live on the 20th floor
?  Are you home all day?  Humans are good and
invented something more powerful than a solar flashlight, called the Sabbath
lift.  Violence is automatic, the whole process does not need to be like that, you can just
go in and stand still, perfectly opened.  What about
today, 2000 years later?  Many people are still stubborn, the ancient
golden phrases spit into modern life, the rules are not over,
but the world has changed, this heavenly book this from life this slowly become the
earth turn.  See we need to find someone to help, another
system.
Well, since this employee handbook is
meant to be affectionate, this one in the handover is handed over to La
.  So a whole body of the orbit is born how to finish it.
La on the hundreds of years of saliva
debate gathered into a book called miss supplement
people specifically is to teach people how to live in the period when the Bible has been outd
yeah, but not out can and hidden
more descendants of these
ค์ dialogue this into a super live this book
Every sentence in the Bible has become an egg of inference
, using new rules to explain the old
rules, using new lawck to pocket the
law all the way to update, here's an example
, tor which sentence is very famous, eye for eye, well
written in ancient times, the original meaning is really self-explanatory, that is, you make
me, so I do
.  Later I do not know how many eight years these pull to walk back out
feed, real justice is not based on recovery, you
can not pay the victim so they re, said the
real meaning of this sentence, in fact, is to solve monetary compensation ah, that is, to
compensate soup contract and mental loss.  Hey, you can't express the
word CEO, so don't express what it means.  Of course, some pulls
say, never misinterpreted right, God originally meant that
, but the facts are now in front of us, every era has its own
set of solutions, who
feels that the latest version after this will not be
pushed back, here, this
point out of it, why to make the whole day output
, is accepted people is not more than want to fire all the
middle wheel
They just changed from one batch of Man to another batch of Man
out, because that old employee manual, simply
not able to do with the modern world, meaning column teaching has the same,
we have a possible scripture in hand, but in the end
scholars are engaged in many different interpretations, including
Islam, stipulates how to pray to do business  It is
so with religion and
scholars of different times, on the madman annotation, get the
result of this respective interpretation, humans do not know which faction, we have
completely fallen into an interpretation trap.  At this
moment this discovery, is so down to not okay,
we need to carry out ate
restructuring
this enterprise from the group was thought up by Christians, they
slowly developed a larger human solution agency, once extremely
strict officials
flocked with the final interpretation of the Bible.  Romanism is the
belief highly centralized, compared to the other two major first-tier religions,
that is, Islam and oil religion are not like heavenly religion.  The
bishops and masters held several super conferences to
clean up the various scriptures that were circulated among the people.   The
official name of the script was directly shot by the TVB executives, and all the official English that does not fit the sound is listed as
such.  From this beginning, humans and face into a multinational
keep this one official, handed over also opened a new
department called the second end to judge the lock that is the
inquisitor specialized in ideological review and
track position.  Since then, quality companies are equivalent to criminals. There is
actually a fact in history. For example, this sixteenth-century Italian scholar
exposed that he was not only reading such books about the infinite universe, but also
openly denied the sacred teachings and stepped on the stage.  As a result, he was
imprisoned for 7 years in Ac, and refused to
speak that day, there is a saying that the church for the mouth of the peak moment for him to
speak this with special and ordered his order, in the end this
scholar who just wants to pursue the truth will die and die, this is the
fate of challenging the official interpretation.  When the big station himself was absolutely
not at fault, this suspicion was guilty, and for the sake of
absolute control, the whole school began to seriously curl up.
At that time, those Confucian scholars, every day at work to run here,
see
how God's ash is interpreting Gus's interpretation Luo's interpretation, and then
themselves and add more search up, that is
internationof
interpretation
interpretation, the whole European
smart son, sun these BRcy inside,
slowly built a giant and mild objective reality is completely
disconnected.  And this one look at the most
I receive mechanism.  Normal people touch the heat naturally will
, but if the company is claiming itself by
a absolutely not wrong spirit manipulated people, how does it
admit that it touched wrong.  The authority of the company will collapse if you admit it wrong
.  The only one to keep the eg social order of the station
, but the real through the left
home became an attractive large group, we will no longer
ask what is true, but instead ask the decision what
is true first this station system this way is good until a
new technology that breaks the sky.
For eight years, this church economy because it relies on manual copying society,
who read what books, which books should be burned
, the Holy See well tracked it, perfect
15th century, printing press out of this, the station from exclusive
to opensource, the same floor almost isolated.   In
just 46 years, this printing press came a full 12 million
books out more than the past 1000 years of hand-copied kind of
consultation officially got rid of the control of the big station thought
that breaking the big station, the truth will definitely win, so yeah too
heavenly dispute, history tells us, Bai proposed the earth
orbit the sun this generation of science, was only bought 0 and a half
years, because the truth is usually good to buy 40
Boring, can't give you emotional value On the contrary, in that era
to buy the market of the middle pole ვით
of witches here, it is a
track line of Catholic financier's extreme conspiracy theory manual very
heavy taste He wrote a Shadan's underground network, said they
know how to sweep tickets and I massage
stir up the dragon  The
content of the book, but the author is very good at playing, he
printed a fake official recommendation in writing. With the book printed by the printing press
, the fake news has penetrated into the hearts of the people.
As a result, courts across Europe, local officials, and
grassroots hunting officials treatment is even all the
standard procedure,
ordinary citizens also began to revenge crazy governor gray, said the next door Len
Shi is female, once opened back to the line, the intention is dead
, they will use red iron
boiling water suspect forced, until you are willing to form some
he will not distinguish between you
reproduce, it will mass-produce information, while
also producing these collectives online, resulting in
up to 50,000 innocent people across Europe being Yan Dong killed.  Let's talk about
1600. This disaster is coming to the
Paperhe family.  Including the mother of the adult
son, and 10-year-old brother c
class judge only 10-year-old with the most extreme form, the official record
is the famous article written to force the child to top their own biological mother experience
source miserable torture of people this all beat
265 people.
Walking that day adults, was red-red to the iron
torn skin flesh man was Che Lun made hands and feet this was let from
below inserted dead in the eyes of the road mother even was life and
death, the whole process of this ten-year-old
forced to see the whole family was mutilated, four months later, he
himself also had to be executed.  How can the whole society have
more such crazy things happening?  Because when the judges die and win
, they don't need to talk about the evidence at all just follow the girl nothing
.  This is the absolutely correct fantasy most place yeah
why the yelling doesn't stop?  Because they can no longer stop, education was
once out of sexual recognition of the existence of women, and
the court has also established a huge official system by not,
if you want to admit that this book is useless, women are not the flow,
that is, recognize the whole sacred body, endlessly murdered tens of thousands of
innocent citizens like P right.  Relying on the power of big corporations with absolutely no fault,
a whole fist and faith will collapse in an instant
.  This is the deepest contradiction in human society.
Since the truth is that no one is qualified to tell,
humans began to ask.  How can we get closer to the truth
?
After experiencing no major disaster, humanity finally wakes up, to find the truth
can no longer rely on absolutely infallible big
one of the big pushers?  It was the Europeans who discovered the new continent
, when the intellectuals heard the collapse feed, it turns out that the earth
has half of the land, species, and humans
are the Bible and those ancient masters Shati frame, however, if the
perfect book, even the earth is missing, so the big station is
not passed down at all, so the starting point of the scientific revolution, is the
first time humans do not know, it turns out that we bravely look in the mirror, it turns out that we bravely look in the mirror
.  Tradition is that Assume
already has the CEO in the hands of the perfect profit frame right, but the scientific
temper just right, he is Assume's current
data is garbage at the moment.  So science is
not lost, only textbooks lose, and textbooks are met
to be changed scholars ari this gave an example, modern
psychology of the Bible DSM this cover is large letter title printed
fifth edition.  This is the official coming out to tell you that this book is
wrong, it is for now, we will continue to
update.  But on the contrary you will never see
a book called Bible 2.0 appear on the market and then come with a x acknowledged
generation of authors into the data, because absolutely correct cow
cladding is not allowed.  But admitting ignorance alone is not enough, there
must also be self-correction mechanisms.  In the 17th century Europe, this set of
mechanisms on
aireb can not read, that is not to believe one side of the meaning.
France also established the Academy of Sciences.  They will not ask you to
publish double will ask some questions how many people read it, how
much money to make, nor will they ask you to financial judge those questions
, do you meet the teachings of Timothy's money book?  They will
only ask your solid where to give the number out, others
can reportodu throw the same result first
when fighting the real SHman this is the human version of it when he found out
that there is no possibility of existence, he was angry to directly throw the door
down the table to study for two more years first, and not
thrown out of the laboratory.  Because in the terms of the time, it is
impossible to say that this conformer can exist at all, even the master who fell twice down the shell length
this public distance.  But this did not shrink, he looked at the
old man and said, the quasi-body I saw was not in a book in
display.  MikeDrop, this statement is the
soul of the scientific revolution.
Dandiscoveryof
course crystalshasa
newcrossplinary
branch
has alsoogivenusindof
how we know in the traditional official?  If you
want you, you have to die to protect the religion. Be
happy, what did the boss say?  You have to give him more seven emotions The
scientific institution is the only one in mankind that will directly
reward you to break through the stage of martial arts
all the teaching subjects, although long, you take long, you are
because you have the ability to push back the former table of gods to the blind, we
are giving up absolute order in exchange for an opportunity to slowly and painfully remove
errors.
The camera is back today, after watching Nexus my biggest
feeling is that our generation Ya Ming holds the
most information in human history, but want to see the Internet, the environment back seems to
degenerate to the middle position, seems to lose the ability to rational discussion
.  Bones and the like, we may still be the
answer, to rely on power to send the center of the original people, a see
different opinions, specify the movement, stick it, force the edge of this kind of
like physiological reflex so hit people impulse, essentially, in
fact, and the year is no different, and many people
to keep those pens know the image of the biography on the Internet
themselves do not know why the official will do this two pieces of money
Seeking is really a very tiring high street labor, and venting
emotions, to obtain the right feeling of the annual price, waste
that part, many people are willing to self-correct this function
, are thrown into the trash can like the end, we will receive
some messages that, you dare not express position I understand, in
some people's eyes so dance seems to be equal to the market
, not really anything special.  Instead, in today's
era of information chaos and everyone is pushing the edge, so walking out to admit
, I do not have enough information to stand on one side before it takes
courage.  The last sentence, or never I must, but
I have a chance is wrong right, today to talk about only
one of the chapters in Nexis I feel the
chapter 唧, the relationship has a lot of colorful stories I have
skipped, the back of the book, in fact, not he I that
reflection there, but his future.  How will Ti
change the way humans pursue the truth?  In this life
, if you are interested in this topic, that is, to
buy back to read, think about whether humans are pursuing the truth itself, or
grasping the truth brings stability?  Finally, if the
polarity is objective, we might as well strike into the objective my
father's
နဲ့